bconnectedonline.com 2019-06-08

# Boyd Gaming Corporation Privacy Policy | BoydGaming.com

**LAST UPDATED:   JANUARY 30, 2018**

Boyd Gaming Corporation is concerned about privacy issues and wants you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose information.  This Privacy Policy describes our practices in connection with information that we collect through our online properties from or in connection with which you are accessing this Privacy Policy, including websites operated by us (the “ **Websites** ”), software applications made available by us for use on or through computers and mobile devices (the “ **Apps** ”), our social media pages that we control (our “ **Social Media Pages** ”), as well as through HTML-formatted email messages that we send to you that link to this Privacy Policy.  This Privacy Policy also applies to information we may collect from our operations, including, but not limited to, our gaming and hotel systems, vacation booking services, and loyalty programs such as the B Connected Loyalty Program (collectively, including the Websites, the Apps and our Social Media Pages, the “ **Services** ”).  By providing Personal Information to us, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.   ****

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**

**Personal Information We May Collect**

“ **Personal Information** ” is information that identifies you as an individual or relates to an identifiable person, including:  

  * Name
  * Postal address (including billing and shipping addresses)
  * Telephone number
  * Email address 
  * Credit and debit card number
  * Profile picture
  * Social media account ID 
  * B Connected account number 
  * Social Security Number
  * Driver’s License Number ****

**How We May Collect Personal Information**

We and our service providers may collect Personal Information in a variety of ways, including: 

  * **Through the Services** :  We may collect Personal Information through the Services, e.g., when you sign up to receive newsletters, offers and promotions, create or log into your account, make a reservation or a purchase, or share information on the Services through your social media account.
  * **Offline** :  We may collect Personal Information from you offline, such as when you visit our casino properties, whether just to visit or transact business, or when you contact customer service.
  * **From Other Sources** :  We may receive your Personal Information from other sources, such as public databases; joint marketing partners; social media platforms; from people with whom you are friends or otherwise connected on social media platforms; as well as from other third parties.  For example, if you elect to connect your social media account to your account with us, such as by signing into your B Connected account using a social network account, certain Personal Information from your social media account will be shared with us, which may include Personal Information that is part of your profile or your friends’ profiles. 

**How We May Use Personal Information**

We may use Personal Information:

  * To respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests, such as to send you newsletters. ****
  * To send administrative information to you, for example, information regarding the Services and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies, or information regarding your gaming activity. 
  * To complete and fulfill your purchase, for example, to process your payments, confirm your reservation, communicate with you regarding a reservation or purchase and provide you with related customer service.
  * To enhance our marketing efforts and to send you marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you.
  * To personalize your experience on the Services by presenting products and offers tailored to you.
  * To allow you to participate in sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions and to administer these activities.  Some of these activities have additional rules, which could contain additional information about how we use and disclose your Personal Information, so we suggest that you read these rules carefully.
  * To allow you to send messages to a friend through the Services.  By using this functionality, you are telling us that you are entitled to use and provide us with your friend’s name and email address. 
  * For our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention, developing new products, enhancing, improving or modifying our Services, enhancing our marketing efforts, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and operating and expanding our business activities. 
  * As we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities, including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates (including through surveillance);(f) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and (g) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain. 

**How Personal Information May Be Disclosed**

Your Personal Information may be disclosed:

  * To our affiliates for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. 
  * To our third party service providers who provide services such as website hosting, data analysis, payment processing, order fulfillment including show and event ticketing, reservation management, information technology and related infrastructure provision, customer service, email delivery, auditing and other services. 
  * To third parties to permit them to send you marketing communications, consistent with your choices. 
  * To third-party sponsors of sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions.
  * To identify you to anyone to whom you send messages through the Services.
  * By you, on message boards, chat, profile pages and blogs and other services to which you are able to post information and materials (including, without limitation, our Social Media Pages).  Please note that any information you post or disclose through these services will become public and may be available to users of the Services and to the general public.  We urge you to be very careful when deciding to disclose your Personal Information, or any other information, on the Services. ****
  * To your friends associated with your social media account, to other website users and to your social media account provider, in connection with your social sharing activity, such as if you connect your social media account to the Services account or log-into your account on the Services through your social media account.  By connecting your Services account and your social media account, you authorize us to share information with your social media account provider, and you understand that the use of the information we share will be governed by the social media site’s privacy policy.  If you do not want your Personal Information shared with other users or with your social media account provider, please do not connect your social media account with your Services account and do not participate in social sharing on the Services.
  * To a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).
  * As we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities, including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; (f) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and (g) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain. 

**OTHER INFORMATION**

**Other Information We May Collect**

“ **Other Information** ” is any information that does not reveal your specific identity or does not directly relate to an individual, such as: 

  * Browser and device information
  * App usage data
  * Information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other technologies
  * Demographic information and other information provided by you
  * Aggregated information

**How We May Collect Other Information**

We and our third party service providers may collect Other Information in a variety of ways, including: 

  * **Through your browser or device** :  Certain information is collected by most browsers or automatically through your device, such as your Media Access Control (MAC) address, computer type (Windows or Macintosh), screen resolution, operating system name and version, device manufacturer and model, language, Internet browser type and version and the name and version of the Services (such as the App) you are using.  We use this information to ensure that the Services function properly. 
  * **Through your use of the App** :  When you download and use the App, we and our service providers may track and collect App usage data, such as the date and time the App on your device accesses our servers and what information and files have been downloaded to the App based on your device number. 
  * **Using cookies** :  Cookies are pieces of information stored directly on the computer that you are using.  Cookies allow us to collect information such as browser type, time spent on the Services, pages visited, language preferences, and other anonymous traffic data.  We and our service providers use the information for security purposes, to facilitate navigation, to display information more effectively, and to personalize your experience while using the Services.  We can recognize your computer to assist your use of the Services.  We also gather statistical information about the usage of the Services in order to continually improve their design and functionality, understand how they are used and to assist us with resolving questions regarding them.  Cookies further allow us to select which of our advertisements or offers are most likely to appeal to you and display them while you are on the Services.  We may also use cookies in online advertising to track responses to our advertisements, and we may use cookies or other files to track your use of other websites for analytics or advertising purposes.

> If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to automatically decline cookies, or be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer to your computer of a particular cookie (or cookies) from a particular site.  You may also wish to refer to <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html>.  However, if you do not accept these cookies, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of the Services.  For example, we may not be able to recognize your computer and you may need to log in every time you visit the applicable Services.  You also may not receive advertising or other offers from us that are relevant to your interests and needs.  ****
> 
> We also use:
> 
>   * Google Analytics, which uses cookies and other, similar technologies to collect and analyze information about use of our Websites and to report on activities and trends.  You can learn about Google Analytics by going to [www.google.com/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/), and opt out by downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, available at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>; and
>   * Adobe's analytics service, which uses cookies and web beacons to help us understand more about the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns.  To learn more, go to: http://www.adobe.com/content/dotcom/en/privacy/analytics.html.  To learn how to opt out, go to <http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html#4>.
> 

> At this time, we do not respond to browser “Do-Not-Track” signals.

  * **Using pixel tags and** **other similar technologies** :  Pixel tags (also known as web beacons and clear GIFs) may be used in connection with some Services to, among other things, track the actions of users of the Services (including email recipients), measure the success of our marketing campaigns and compile statistics about usage of the Services and response rates. 

  * **IP Address** :  Your “ **IP Address** ” is a number that is automatically assigned to the computer that you are using by your Internet Service Provider (ISP).  An IP Address may be identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever a user accesses the Services, along with the time of the visit and the page(s) that were visited.  Collecting IP Addresses is standard practice and is done automatically by many websites, applications and other services.  We use IP Addresses for purposes such as calculating usage levels of the Services, helping diagnose server problems, and administering the Services.

  * **Physical Location:**   We may collect the physical location of your device by, for example, using satellite, cell phone tower or WiFi signals.  We may use your device’s physical location to provide you with personalized location-based services and content, including specific information about our Services if you are in physical proximity to one of our properties and have opted into receiving text messages from us.  We may also share your device’s physical location, combined with information about what advertisements you viewed and other information we collect, with our marketing partners to enable them to provide you with more personalized content and to study the effectiveness of advertising campaigns.  In some instances, you may be permitted to allow or deny such uses and/or sharing of your device’s location, but if you choose to deny such uses and/or sharing, we and/or our marketing partners may not be able to provide you with the applicable personalized services and content.

  * **From you** :  Other information, such as your preferred means of communication, is collected when you voluntarily provide it. 

  * **By aggregating information** :  Aggregated Personal Information does not personally identify you or any other user of the Services (for example, we may aggregate Personal Information to calculate the percentage of our users who have a particular telephone area code).

**How We May Use and Disclose Other Information**

We may use and disclose Other Information for any purpose, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law.  If we are required to treat Other Information as Personal Information under applicable law, then we may use it for all the purposes for which we use and disclose Personal Information. 

In some instances, we may combine Other Information with Personal Information.  If we do, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information as long as it is combined.

**THIRD PARTY SERVICES**

This Privacy Policy does not address, and we are not responsible for, the privacy, information or other practices of any third parties, including any third party operating any site or service to which the Services link.  The inclusion of a link on the Services does not imply endorsement of the linked site or service by us or by our affiliates. 

We are not responsible for the information collection, usage, disclosure or security policies and practices of other organizations, such as Facebook, Apple, Google, Microsoft, Twitter, Pinterest, and Foursquare, or any other app developer, app provider, social media platform provider, operating system provider, wireless service provider or device manufacturer. 

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISERS**

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements regarding goods and services that may be of interest to you when you access and use the Services and other websites, based on information relating to your access to and use of the Services and other websites.  To do so, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser (including through the use of pixel tags).  If you would like more information about this practice, including your choices in connection with it, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> and <http://www.aboutads.info/>.

**SECURITY**

We seek to use reasonable organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect Personal Information within our organization.  Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised), please immediately notify us in accordance with the _“Contacting Us”_ section below.

**CHOICES AND ACCESS**

**Your choices regarding our use of your Personal Information**

We give you choices regarding our use of your Personal Information for marketing purposes.  You may opt-out from: 

  * **Receiving electronic communications from us** :  If you no longer want to receive marketing-related emails from us on a going-forward basis, you may opt-out by clicking on the unsubscribe link in these emails.  You may also opt out by visiting <http://www.boydgaming.com/unsubscribe> and, if you are a B Connected member, by visiting <https://www.bconnectedonline.com/> to sign in and update your profile. 

  * **Receiving SMS text messages from us** :  If you no longer want to receive SMS marketing text messages at a telephone number that you have provided to us for purposes of receiving such offers, text the word “STOP” to the 51552 short code from the phone number you want to have removed from any future marketing **** alerts or offers. 

  * **Our sharing of your Personal Information with affiliates for their direct marketing purposes** :  If you would prefer that we do not share your Personal Information on a going-forward basis with our affiliates for their direct marketing purposes, you may opt-out of this sharing by emailing us at [privacypolicy@boydgaming.com](mailto:privacypolicy@boydgaming.com).

We will try to comply with your request(s) as soon as reasonably practicable.  Please note that if you opt-out of receiving marketing-related emails from us, we may still send you important administrative messages, from which you cannot opt-out.

**How you can access, change or suppress your Personal Information   **

If you would like to review, correct, or update Personal Information that you have previously provided us, you may contact us in person, by visiting any Boyd Gaming Casino and speaking to a customer service representative, emailing us at [privacypolicy@boydgaming.com](mailto:privacypolicy@boydgaming.com) or, if you are a B Connected Member, by visiting [http://www.bconnectedonline.com](http://www.bconnectedonline.com/). 

In your request, please make clear what Personal Information you would like to have changed or updated.  For your protection, we may only implement requests with respect to the Personal Information associated with the particular email address that you use to send us your request, and we may need to verify your identity before implementing your request.  Subject to applicable laws, including but not limited to our obligations relating to anti-money laundering laws, we will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. 

In addition, please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions that you began prior to requesting such change (e.g., when you make a reservation or enter a promotion, you may not be able to change the Personal Information provided until after the completion of such reservation or promotion).  There may also be residual information that will remain within our databases and other records, which will not be removed.

**USE OF SERVICES BY INDIVIDUALS UNDER THE APPROPRIATE AGE**

Persons under the age of twenty-one (21) are not permitted to gamble at Boyd Gaming properties nor loiter on any Boyd Gaming casino properties located in the United States.  Any offers made or contests we conduct, unless otherwise noted, are not open to persons younger than the legal gaming age in the applicable jurisdiction (typically 21).  Persons younger than this legal age are not allowed to use our websites, accept offers, or win contests, and we do not knowingly collect information from such persons for gaming-related offers.  We reserve the right to verify age at any time for any reason and may decline to provide products, services or access rights to any person who does not have valid age identification.  Please note that for some of our properties, users may access limited aspects of the Services in compliance with applicable local laws.  (By way of example, certain family-oriented events may take place at such properties).

**USE OF SERVICES BY INDIVIDUALS UNDER 13**

In no way are the Services directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13), and we do not knowingly collect personal information online from such individuals.

**CROSS-BORDER TRANSFER**

The Services are controlled and operated by us from the United States, and are not intended to subject us to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country or territory other than that of the United States.  Your Personal Information may be stored and processed in any country where we have facilities or in which we engage service providers, and by using the Services you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside of your country of residence, including the United States, which may have different data protection rules than those of your country.

**SENSITIVE INFORMATION**

we ask that you not send us, and you not disclose, any sensitive Personal Information unless specifically requested ( _e.g._ , social security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, biometrics or genetic characteristics, or criminal background) on or through the Services or otherwise to us.

**UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We may change this Privacy Policy.  The “ _Last Updated_ ” legend at the top of this page indicates when this Privacy Policy was last revised.  Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the Services.  Your use of the Services following these changes means that you accept the revised Privacy Policy. ****

**CONTACTING US**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacypolicy@boydgaming.com](mailto:privacypolicy@boydgaming.com) or:

Boyd Gaming Corporate Office  
ATTN.: Privacy Policy   
3883 Howard Hughes Parkway  
Ninth Floor  
Las Vegas, NV 89169  ****

PLEASE NOTE THAT EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS ARE NOT ALWAYS SECURE; SO PLEASE DO NOT INCLUDE CREDIT CARD OR OTHER SENSITIVE INFORMATION IN YOUR EMAILS TO US.
